(Sheldon:)Leonard made me soup,
and I was mean to him.
(Sheldon:)I was mean to him.
(Sheldon:)He must have felt terrible.
(Sheldon:)Oh, now I feel terrible.
Neat!
(Amy:)Glad I could help.
(Sheldon:)Now let me see you
feel bad for lying
(Sheldon:)and staying in Detroit
longer than you needed to.
(flatly):
I feel so, so bad.
(Sheldon:)Hey, we're both great at this.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, get ready
for an apology.
(Sheldon:)And with the added twist
of an M. Night Shyamalan movie,
(Sheldon:)I'm going to mean it.
(Leonard:)Ah, so like every other
(Sheldon:)M. Night Shyamalan movie
I've seen,
(Leonard:)you spoil it in advance.
(Sheldon:)Hey, if you didn't know
Bruce Willis
(Sheldon:)was dead the whole time,
that's not on me.
(Raj:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Here it comes.
(Sheldon:)You tried to take care of me
(Sheldon:)when I was sick,
and I was mean to you.